// this will be the array of my questions
const quizQuestions = [{
        question: 'What type of farm does Dwight own?',
        choices: ["Bear Farm", "Beet Farm", "Apple Farm", "Banana Farm"],
        rightAnswer: "Beet Farm"



    },
    {
        question: 'How long were Pam and Roy engaged?',
        choices: ["3 Years", "6 Years", "24 Months", "2 Years"],
        rightAnswer: "3 Years"



    },
    {
        question: 'Which of Angelas cats does Dwight kill?',
        choices: ["Bandito", "Stinky", "Sprinkles", "Captain"],
        rightAnswer: "Sprinkles"



    },
    {
        question: 'Who started the fire in The Office?',
        choices: ["Ryan", "Kevin", "IT guy", "Jim"],
        rightAnswer: "Ryan"



    },
    {
        question: 'What type of car does Dwight drive?',
        choices: ["Spaceship", "Vespa", "Pontiac Trans Am", "Camaro"],
        rightAnswer: "Pontiac Trans Am"



    },
    {
        question: 'What is Scrantons Nickname?',
        choices: ["Oh my god this town is on fire", "Beetlejuice Village", "The Sad city", "The Electric City"],
        rightAnswer: "The Electric City"



    },
    {
        question: 'Whose mother does Michael date?',
        choices: ["Your mom", "Angela", "Jim", "Pam"],
        rightAnswer: "Pam"



    },
    {
        question: 'Who was snubbed from playing on Michaels basketball team?',
        choices: ["Stanley", "Kevin", "Angela", "Pam"],
        rightAnswer: "Kevin"



    },
    {
        question: 'Where do Michael and Jan spend a Christmas vacation together?',
        choices: ["Jamaica", "Mexico", "Italy", "Home"],
        rightAnswer: "Jamaica"



    },
    {
        question: 'What does Michael burn his foot on?',
        choices: ["Stove", "The sun", "George Foreman grill", "Printer"],
        rightAnswer: "George Foreman grill"



    },
    {
        question: 'Who pooped on Michaels carpet?',
        choices: ["It was a group effort", "Roy", " Todd Packer", "Pam"],
        rightAnswer: "Todd Packer"



    },
    {
        question: 'Which office employee did Michael hit with his car?',
        choices: ["Meredith", "Himself", "Jim", "IT guy"],
        rightAnswer: "Meredith"



    }
];
// This is where i need to create the array for my giphys
//this one will be for correct answers
const funImages = [
    './assets/images/dancingwin.gif',
    './assets/images/itstruewin.gif',
    './assets/images/naileditwin.gif',
    './assets/images/highfivewin.gif',
    './assets/images/poppinbottleswin.gif',
    './assets/images/raisetheroofwin.gif',
];
// this one is for incorrect answers
const sadImages = [
    './assets/images/dontlikelost.gif',
    './assets/images/boomloser.gif',
    './assets/images/worstlost.gif',
    './assets/images/frustratedlost.gif',
    './assets/images/loserlost.gif',
    './assets/images/notspeciallost.gif',

];